I'm scared, Joe.
I'm scared for you.
I'm scared for our daughters.
♪ tense music ♪
[Joe]
What did you sell them?
[Cade]
Whatever he's looking for.
He owns my fucking degree.
My whole future.
Not anymore, he doesn't.
We hold it now.
So you get something,
you send him a text,
he sends you an address
and you meet him there.
- Is that it?
- [Cade] Yes.
♪
Green light.
Green light, let's go.
What the fuck!? [yells]
[whimpering]
When you're found guilty,
life imprisonment times three.
Understand the game?
Trade information for freedom.
We began our operation
targeting known assets
of Russian Intelligence.
Which brings us to the question,
is our national security
at risk?
Without a question.
♪ dramatic music ♪
[exhales]
♪
[muffled grunting]
♪ tense, somber music ♪
[helicopter whirring]
[Cruz] Getting real fucking
bored of this stateside gig.
What are you talking about?
You just karate-chopped
some fucker last night.
- The schoolteacher?
- Yeah.
[clicks tongue]
Fuck that. That ain't a fight.
[laughs softly] She's got a lot
of pent-up aggression, this one.
[chuckles]
We are all very aware of that.
Hey, we go
wherever the fight is.
Right now, it has us here, so...
I mean, shit, I don't mind
a few soft targets,
'cause you know
the hard targets are coming.
They always do.
Agents of FBI's
counterintelligence unit
engaged in an operation
that spanned five states
and resulted in multiple arrests
in what the Department
of Justice is claiming
represents the largest
sting operation
since the Abscam operation
in 1978,
which led to the arrest
and conviction
of seven members of Congress,
- the mayor of Camden...
- Well, you weren't kidding.
...and three Philadelphia
City Council members.
While no public officials have
been arrested to this point...
What have I told you
about the news, babe?
- ...high-ranking members...
- It's a boat fire.
Boat fire?
What do the rats do
when the boat's on fire?
- ...have been arrested.
- They jump ship.
So, you're telling me
they weren't really arrested?
Oh, yeah, they were arrested.
So, that... it's true?
It's a sliver of the truth.
Now the news will try
to discredit it.
- Well, why would they do that?
- [laughs softly]
'Cause it's what they do.
The news is the propaganda arm
of whoever
has the greatest influence over
the organization reporting it.
[exhales] Wow. When did
they get control of the news?
It's always been this way.
I mean,
read the New York Times version
of the Battle of Gettysburg,
and then a newspaper
in Atlanta's version
and tell me
it's the same battle.
They call it "stories"
for a reason.
Honey. Are we close?
To this being over for us?
We're close.
[Joe]
How we doing?
Peachy.
Yeah?
[stifled laugh]
Don't look too peachy.
Yeah, we're, uh,
peachy on the inside.
What if I told you guys...
...that we can go home soon?
How peachy would you be then?
- Really?
- Mm-hmm. Really.
Uh, is it safe?
Honey, I wouldn't take us home
if it wasn't.
When do we get to go home?
In a few days, I think.
I know it's been hard,
and I'm sorry.
You guys have been
such troopers.
Do you ever think about them?
Who?
The men that came to our house.
♪ slow, somber music ♪
- Not at all?
- Not for a second.
And I don't want you
to think about them, either.
They don't deserve your fear.
And they forfeited their right
to your compassion.
The only thing they deserve
is to be forgotten.
♪ tense, atmospheric music ♪
[loud chatter]
[sighs]
- Hey.
- [Joe] Good morning.
- Good morning.
[sighs]
This is my favorite place
in D.C.
- Really?
- Yeah.
[Mullins] Name another saloon
that serves eggs Chesapeake.
Hell, name another saloon
that serves breakfast,
- for that matter.
- [chuckles]
McKinley, Grant...
- Mm.
- ...Cleveland, Roosevelt.
[Mullins] Every one of them
stood at that bar.
Fitting place
to end the career of a man
who has forsaken the oath
he swore--
that we all swore-- to uphold.
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't
really looking forward to this.
[Meade chuckles]
[door opens]
I'll start us off,
and then I will
let you all explain
- his lack of options, okay?
- Yes, sir.
[Mullins]
I just want to sit back
and watch.
Have a seat, Ryan.
[grunts] You said "breakfast,"
not "breakfast meeting."
Every meal is a meeting
in this town, Ryan.
- You know that.
- [Olson] Yeah.
So, what is this meeting about?
Uh, I'm on Foreign Relations,
not Intelligence.
[Meade]
We had an agent come in
from the cold.
Come in from the cold?
Mm-hmm.
[Olson]
I'm not sure I follow you.
[Mullins]
Not familiar with that term?
I am not.
[Westfield]
It's a reference
to either one of our officers
who's been acting
as a double agent
returning from that mission,
or, in this instance,
a Russian SVR agent
who has flipped
and come to our side.
- "Flipped."
- Defected.
Hmm. Hmm.
And where is this agent now?
We're holding them
at the Farm for now.
After our debrief,
we're gonna move them
into WitPro, most likely.
Well...
Good.
I hope she gives you
some good intel.
[chuckles]
- Something funny?
- Yeah, something's funny.
[Olson]
Care to share?
Well, you fucked up right there.
You know that, right?
- Excuse me?
- I said,
you fucked up.
You can't talk to me like that.
I'm a sitting U.S. senator.
Not for long.
- Who is this?
- She's the senior case officer
who was assigned to you.
"Assigned" to me? To do what?
[Joe]
To oversee your resignation.
But let's back up a little bit.
Let's talk about
how you fucked up.
Enlighten me.
Sure.
We said "foreign agent."
You said "she."
How'd you know
the agent is female?
♪ slow, tense music ♪
How'd you know that, Ryan?
How'd you know?
[Meade] The agent in question
provided us,
among others,
you as one of her assets.
- [scoffs] That's ridiculous.
- Oh, really?
Well, she also provided us
with wire transfers
to an account
in the Altajir Bank branch,
George Town, Cayman Islands,
under the name St. Paul
Alliance Ventures, LLC.
S.P.A.V. then made
sizable contributions
to various nonprofits, uh,
PTP, Emerge, Think Left,
who then made contributions
to your campaign.
Which is a violation
of Title 18,
United States Code Section 793.
Which is treason, Ryan.
[Westfield clears throat]
What we are here to do
is present you with two options.
Option one:
you resign, tomorrow.
Not in three days, not even two.
Tomorrow.
You will publicly resign
at this press conference.
You will not seek any work
in the private sector,
industries of defense,
media, education,
lobbying in any form.
You may not seek any office
on the state or municipal level.
You may not practice law
and you will not sit
on the board
of any publicly traded company.
Option two:
you refuse option one
or violate
any of option one's parameters,
and that is your future.
You will be arrested
and prosecuted
to the fullest extent
of the law.
The government will seize
all of your assets
for nonpayment of taxes
on the funds
that you accepted illegally.
We will ensure that your family
shares in the suffering,
as they most certainly
benefited from the crimes
that you took
against this nation.
And we will release
your offenses to the public
and do irreparable harm
to your name
and your family's name.
Choice is yours.
But we need your choice
and we need it now
or we choose for you.
What reason do I give
for resigning?
- What's the reason?
- I don't care.
- It's your decision.
- [stammers]
What do I tell my family?
[Meade]
I would suggest that you lie.
Seems to come
naturally to you.
[Westfield]
Say it's for health reasons.
Then go to your doctor
and fucking find one.
[Meade]
There you go.
[Mullins]
Look at me, Ryan.
Sinking in, isn't it?
Yeah.
Tomorrow, Ryan.
We'll be watching.
[Meade]
Great.
There is a third option.
You could kill yourself.
♪ dark, tense music ♪
That gets my vote.
Think about it.
♪ dramatic, haunting music ♪
♪
♪ atmospheric, pulsing music ♪
[engine starts]
Oh, he's looking right at you.
Yeah.
Guess this ain't a soft tail.
Nah.
We want him to know:
where he goes, we go.
[engine revs]
[weatherman] We have 55 degrees
currently for Downtown Metro,
67 our high today...
[tires screech]
...by Saturday...
[tires screeching]
[announcer] Back in six minutes
with more traffic updates.
[reporter] As more information
is released regarding
the espionage ring
that has rocked Washington,
we are joined by former FBI
Deputy Director Harold Cisneros
to help us better understand
this crisis as it unfolds.
Mr. Cisneros,
thank you for joining us.
[Cisneros]
Thank you for having me.
[reporter]
The biggest questions are,
how far-reaching do you think
this scandal goes,
and do you think
this is just the beginning?
[Cisneros] Oh, definitely.
There has always been espionage
and counterespionage playing
itself out in Washington,
as there is in London,
Moscow, Mexico City
and every other center
of national government.
Intelligence agencies
essentially have
a blank check
to peddle influence
on the political theater
of their adversaries.
And there's always people,
whether they're financially,
politically,
or ideologically motivated
who are willing
to benefit our adversaries
for the betterment
of themselves.
[reporter] So, you expect
more names to be released?
[Cisneros] Absolutely.
What you'll start seeing soon
is a rash of resignations
from within the government,
as well as the industries
that service the government.
[engine revs]
Well, what's been
most surprising to me
is that foreign influence
has now been directly tied
to our higher learning
institutions.
That shows that Russia,
China our adversaries
in the Middle East are willing
to play an extremely long game
of whittling away
at the core values
this nation was founded on
over generations.
[reporter] And creating
a real crisis of confidence
in institutions
that have typically
been considered infallible.
Our universities,
news organizations,
elected officials,
and judiciary--
[Cisneros] The very bedrock
of our civilization
is now called into question
and will be
very closely scrutinized.
And it appears
that scrutiny is warran--
[radio shuts off]
[device chimes]
Call my wife.
[automated voice]
Calling wife mobile.
- [line ringing]
- Cancel!
[device beeps]
Fuck.
♪ slow, tense music ♪
[device chimes]
Call Evan Chambers.
Calling Evan Chambers,
chief of staff.
[line ringing]
[Evan over phone]
Yes, sir?
Senator?
[device beeps]
[screams]
♪ tense, dramatic music ♪
- [phone beeping]
- [automated voice] Call from
- Evan Chambers, chief of--
- [device beeps]
- [engine revs]
- [tires screech]
- He's running. Dumb fuck.
- Shit.
He's driving
the wrong way to hold
the press conference,
I'll say that.
Boss.
- [Joe over phone] Yeah?
- Our senator's on the run.
[tires screeching]
We're northbound
on Wisconsin doing 100.
Maybe have Metro PD intercept.
Chickenshit.
I guess he wants to do this
the hard way.
Pull him over if you can.
I'll get MPD en route.
Copy.
[siren wails]
Are we playing
law enforcement now?
It's the badge
in your left pocket.
[tires screech]
What the hell is he doing?
♪
[seatbelt unbuckles]
[horn honks, blares]
What the fuck?
[panicked chatter]
Coward's way out.
Hey, boss?
Our guy parked his Mercedes
in oncoming traffic.
Head-on with a tractor trailer.
- Boss!
- Is he dead?
He ain't walking away
from this one.
Hell, I doubt the truck driver
makes it, either.
Don't wait around to find out.
Copy.
[sighs]
Piece of shit.
He got off easy.
♪ slow, somber music
[Tucker]
Damn.
Son of a bitch.
[indistinct radio chatter]
- ♪ slow, tense music
- [siren whoops]
[reporter] As the espionage
scandal that has rocked
both Washington, D.C.,
and the nation
continues to expand,
federal officials have now
surrounded the embassy
of the Russian Federation,
refusing to let anyone enter
or leave the premises.
Arrest totals are
now in the dozens.
Two members of
the House of Representatives
have already announced
their resignation,
and four other members were
arrested at the Capitol
by members
of the FBI's counterterrorism
and counterespionage unit.
While the White House has not
made an official statement
- as of yet...
- Won't they just do
- to our embassy in Moscow?
- ...both the Russian...
Mm-hmm.
We'll walk it back some.
...both have
their diplomatic visas...
The foreign minister
is out, for sure.
What we really want
is to clear out
those mid-level diplomats.
Those are
the real operators, anyway.
- Yeah.
- [reporter] This just in:
Senator Ryan Olson was involved
in a head-on collision
along Wisconsin Avenue.
Witnesses on the scene claim
Senator Olson was being pursued
by federal agents
when he lost control
of his vehicle
and veered
into oncoming traffic,
striking a truck driver
in the southbound lane.
The senator was pronounced dead
at the scene,
and the truck driver,
whose name is being withheld,
has been transferred
to George Washington
- University Hospital.
- [Mullins] Damn.
What's the total of arrests
so far?
Thirty-seven so far,
another 23 foreign agents
without FSIA protections.
[Hollar]
This is a political disaster.
Maybe not.
Our administration
discovered this.
Most of these foreign assets
were in position
when POTUS took office.
I say we lay the blame
with the previous
administration.
[Hollar]
Mm-hmm. They made the mess,
- we cleaned it up.
- [Westfield] We could blame it
on their reduction
in federal funding of police.
Has FBI's counterintelligence
budget been cut?
Up 8% every year since 2011,
although we don't have
to be so specific.
Well, quite the find,
your double agent, Kyle.
I'd say she over-delivered,
yes, sir.
Where is she now?
She's in WitPro, sir.
[Mullins]
Sure was useful.
No way we can keep her around?
They would kill her, sir.
[Westfield]
This is one arena where Russia
will accept whatever
consequences come
just to make that statement
to the other agents.
I would be surprised
if a missile didn't find its way
to her family's home
in Kyiv within the week.
May I have an opinion on this?
[Meade]
Uh, you may have an opinion,
but I recommend
that you don't share it, Kyle.
Well, I'd like to hear it.
Sure.
[clears throat]
[tongue clicks]
She's probably dead anyway.
WitPro's great for some wiseguy
who rats out his bosses, but...
SVR and MSS,
they can go through DOJ,
FBI, IRS and GSA databases,
narrow the search
to one of about 300 locations,
and have her exact location
in a matter of weeks,
and we'll never
even know they looked.
Why not put her on the payroll?
Keep her at the Farm
or Bragg or Campbell.
I mean, they ain't getting
to her on a fucking SF base.
Language, Kyle.
Sorry.
Look, we've only debriefed her
for this operation
and the operation in Ukraine.
We have not debriefed her
with the goal
of a broader understanding
of SVR operations,
their intelligence structure
in Europe,
Middle East,
in Venezuela, Colombia.
You think Russia
can find her in WitPro?
I guarantee it.
Byron?
I think there's
real intelligence value
to working with her, yes.
Uh, how long
will she be willing to live
with extremely limited mobility?
No social life whatsoever?
A-And not to mention
that WitPro
is what she asked for,
and it's what we agreed to.
Find out if she'd be willing.
All right.
Well, of course,
we've got to find her.
FBI won't tell us.
DOJ is not going
to divulge her location
or her new identity.
♪ tense, atmospheric music ♪
[Mullins]
Well, Kyle...
you seem confident that
everybody else can find her.
Now you get to find her.
Yes, sir.
Good. All right,
that's it, everybody.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
- [throat clears]
- [Meade] Great.
Thank you, sir.
[clears throat]
Good work.
Okay. That's why you keep
your opinions to yourself, Kyle.
Have fun hunting
all over Scottsdale
and Denver and fucking Orlando.
And what's-what's the island
off the coast of Washington
where they stick
all those WitPro misfits?
San Juan.
Oh, yeah.
Have fun on that one, huh?
Make sure you pack a coat.
[whispers]
Fuck.
[reporter] Hundreds of
Russian embassy diplomats are
being escorted out
of the building
by federal officials
as we speak,
and it is unclear
at this time...
Guess the rats jumped ship.
Yep.
[Neal]
What's with the buses?
When a diplomatic visa's
canceled,
the revocation is immediate.
That's a one-way ride
to the airport.
[Kate]
Uh, Mom,
what's going on? This is crazy.
- What's crazy?
- I'm, uh, I'm watching
the news on TikTok.
Kate, there's no news on TikTok.
I mean, it's the same news
as that.
[Joe] That's not news, either.
That's...
conversation for another time.
What that is
is people who value
their pocketbook
and their worldview
over your safety
and your freedom
getting exactly
what they deserve.
- A-And what do they deserve?
- You know what,
let's not talk about
what it means for them,
let's talk about what it means
for you and your sister
and your dad and me.
"Your dad and I."
Really?
- [chuckles]
- [Joe] We're gonna do that?
Okay, I'm sorry... I'm sorry,
I'm sorry. What...
What does it mean for us?
It means you get to go home.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Like, for real, it's safe?
Everybody that wanted to hurt me
is being loaded on that bus.
And they're not
coming back, baby.
Okay. Wow.
Well, I-I should pack.
Yeah. Go tell Charlie.
[laughs]
[Kate] Uh, Charlie,
come on, let's get packed!
We're going home!
You never took
that gun class, did you?
- No.
- You asshole,
with your moral integrity.
Honey, you are the soldier.
I'm not the soldier.
- I'm the opposite.
- [laughs softly]
That was paternal.
- You liked it?
- No, I hated it.
If you're going to kiss me,
kiss me on the lips.
God, you soldiers
are so bossy.
Well, that's not
the soldier in me.
That's the Dominican in me,
and you don't want
to wake up that side
after the fucking month
I've been through.
Oh, the month
that you've been through?
[scoffs] Okay, I'm gonna start
to talk with my hands...
- Mm.
- ...and then my neck
- is gonna start to move...
- [chuckles]
...and then you're fucked, buddy.
I love it when you move
your neck.
It's fucking terrifying,
but it's hot.
- So arousing.
- [both chuckling]
- [Joe chuckles]
- Of course it is.
[conversing indistinctly]
[whispers]
Why are they laughing?
Who cares? They're laughing.
[both laughing]
- [voices speak quietly]
- ♪ slow, atmospheric music ♪
[soft grunt]
[insects trilling]
[pop song playing over speakers]
[clears throat]
[device beeping]
[chimes]
- [clerk] Have a blessed day.
- Thank you.
Good morning.
[dog barking nearby]
[children cheering nearby]
[deadbolt clacks]
[sighs]
♪ slow, suspenseful music ♪
[gasps]
- No need for that.
- [panting]
We're on the same side,
I thought.
I'll get eyes out front.
Have a seat.
How did you know I am here?
Yeah, that was a trick
to figure out,
I'm not gonna lie to you.
[door closes]
What's happened?
[Kyle sighs]
Do they know about me?
No.
Russian contract agents took
one of our senior case officers.
Your senior case officer.
Joe?
Wait. Took her?
Abducted her?
Just outside her house
Monday morning.
Last Monday?
Today is day six.
What do they want?
Don't know.
They haven't reached out?
Not a fucking word.
Do you still have Yurimov?
Maybe.
What was their reaction
to you holding him?
They don't know.
The plan is to offer
that chip today.
[Oleksandra sighs]
- They don't know.
What do you know
about the abductors?
Nothing. We assume
Belarus contract agents
'cause that's who made
the first attempt.
Tracked 'em to a safe house
in Maryland, then to an FBO.
They put her on a jet,
didn't register the flight,
flew below the hard deck.
We don't know the destination
of the plane.
- What kind of plane?
- Challenger 300.
Our best guess is,
they switch her to a plane
and cross the Atlantic,
unless you think Cuba,
- and they go King Air, fly low.
- No.
You own the air.
And you're monitoring
all the flights
- over the ocean now, yes?
- Mm-hmm.
And any plane
without a flight plan,
- you intercept.
- Correct.
Yeah, no, that's not
how Russian Intelligence works.
That's too many risks.
No upside
if not trading for Yurimov.
I mean, Putin is terrified
of direct confrontation
with the U.S.
Help us fill in the gaps here.
Okay.
Well, our operations took out
most of their agents
with diplomatic immunity and
Russian Federation credentials.
That leaves contract agents
from Belarus, from Iran.
There's cooperation with China,
but MSS would never assist
in direct action.
All the safe houses
are still in play,
and Belarus contract agents
know about them
and have access to them.
But someone in Russian embassy
is overseeing.
I don't know why.
Well, money's a hell
of a motivator.
Would a Russian case officer
go off the reservation
for enough money?
Eh, I don't know. Maybe.
But who would pay
that kind of money?
This operation
would cost millions.
And the fee,
I mean, to abduct a senior
case officer on U.S. soil
and deliver overseas,
that's 50...
$100 million-dollar operation.
Who can afford that?
Muslim Brotherhood.
Qatar, but only as proxy.
They would never
directly fund this.
Iran?
Wait.
Nothing we did
had any effect on Iran.
We uncovered
none of their agents,
their intelligence network, nothing.
But Iran is the only nation
that plays such a short game.
Has she overseen any operations
against Iran in the past?
Ah.
Okay.
Let's say she has.
The greater success
her operation had,
the more motivated Iran would be
to act against her.
Iran's foreign policy is revenge
and perception of strength--
not to us-- to their own people.
And if you burn Iran bad enough,
Iran is gonna want to burn back.
Would they use
Belarus contract agents?
Oh, my God,
they would use anyone
who would take their money,
and Belarussians?
[scoffs]
They're cowboys.
Russia's frozen here now,
no operations,
and Belarus contract agents
have no cover careers.
They have no source of income
other than the one
they generate.
If they have access
to Russian assets--
If they have
a Russian officer involved,
they have access to everything.
All right.
- So they get overseas.
- Mm-hmm.
Where?
Iran.
They depart from where?
We would look for FBOs
near major airports
with lots of air traffic,
but stay outside of it.
Fastest course
to international waters.
Mm, Florida's no good.
Too much DEAs,
too much Air Force bases.
Too many eyes
on international flights.
We would use Houston FBOs.
Kleberg County Regional has
a 6,000-foot runway.
No customs, no ATC.
20 minutes to Mexican airspace.
Then you skirt south
of Cuban airspace
because it's monitored by U.S.
And then you're
in international airspace
within an hour.
And then you reposition.
Only a Global 8000
has that kind of range.
When did they fly her out
of Maryland?
Yesterday.
You might be out of time.
[exhales]
They wouldn't move her
unless they had an out
ready to execute.
Were safe houses in the region
on your computer?
Yeah, everything.
But it'll be three or four
in a neighborhood,
always in a cluster
and never the same one twice.
All right,
use the Signal account.
I want a complete breakdown
of their S.O.P.s
in hostage removal
and retrieval.
Text Jenny B in the contacts.
♪ ominous music ♪
Looking for a Global 7500
or 8000,
Gulfstream 700, Falcon 8X.
Most likely departing an FBO
in and around Houston
or South Texas.
[tires squeal]
♪ tense, dramatic music ♪
♪
We are en route
to George Bush Intercontinental.
Intelligence suggests
that the most likely
escape route
is the shortest distance
into Mexican airspace.
Inside, you'll find a list of
both public and private airports
capable of accommodating
a jet large enough
to make a transatlantic flight
to the Middle East,
Belarus or Russia.
There are currently 54 jets
in the region capable
of making such a flight.
NSA is combing through
flight plans and manifests
and will alert us
as information is processed.
Page two is a map of safe houses
in the towns
of Beaumont,
Clear Lake, Katy,
Sugar Land,
The Woodlands, Conroe.
[Two Cups] Jesus,
there's a hundred of them.
Russian SVR has used
Kleberg County Regional before.
Kyle and a ground branch
detachment is en route now.
What's your plan of action?
[Amber]
FBI, HRT
and HSI are all standing by
at the Justice Center
in Houston.
We are also positioning
a Texas Ranger SOG team
at the Houston
Executive Airport.
We have a Little Bird
waiting for us
at Joint Reserve Base Ellington.
Josie, you will be on standby
with that helo
along with Cruz, Two Cups,
Bobby and Tucker.
You are QRF. Tex and Randy,
you will recon safe houses
in Sugar Land,
Pearland and Missouri City.
You're running plates
at all those locations.
If the vehicles come back
a rental car, it's a red flag.
If it comes back out of state,
red flag.
If it is owned by an LLC,
it is a red flag.
Houston SWAT is on notice,
and patrol vehicles
have been notified
to be mindful
of a human smuggling effort
in the region
and to pay close attention
to traffic stops
involving SUVs, vans, U-Hauls,
anything that could transport
cargo and a detail.
Our best hope
is that we get lucky
and we intercept them
at a safe house or in transit
to an FBO.
Once they get her up in the air,
our options
are extremely limited,
even if we do identify
the plane.
Our intelligence source
has informed us
that they run covert exfils
over seven-day cycles.
So the first three days is
moving safe house to safe house.
They're learning our
reaction time, our capabilities.
Day five, they move by air,
they prep for exfil.
Day six, they hand the asset
over to the transit team,
and then that team takes her
the rest of the way.
Now, that transit team
has most certainly filed
flight plans and manifests
that will withstand scrutiny.
So we need to catch them
at a safe house,
in transit to an FBO,
or entering an FBO.
We're talking a jet
of a range of 7,000 miles.
That's a 6,000-foot runway
at minimum,
and that's pushing it.
Seven thousand
is more realistic.
Are there any FBOs in the area
- that could accommodate that?
- There's six.
Six in the region and then five
within a 100-mile radius.
And you got HRT or SWAT
at all these airports?
- Correct.
- [Randy] Let's say we do
get lucky,
stumble upon their safe house.
We holding in place for a QRF,
or are we engaging
as a two-man team?
You're gonna have to make
that call on the ground.
But if you think
you can retrieve her,
then you give it your best shot.
[Bobby]
But superior numbers
is our best shot
for a retrieval.
[Amber] Her transport team
is likely three-man,
also traveling
extremely low-vis,
so sidearms is most likely
the primary weapon in this case.
Understand,
if they get her up in the air
and we have not identified
that plane, she is dead.
♪ slow, somber music ♪
Even if we do successfully
identify the plane...
...we will engage with
that plane, and she is dead.
Her only hope at this point is
that we move on a safe house
or a vehicle interdiction.
[Cruz]
Got to give me a chance, God.
Give me a chance
to get in there.
I'll get her.
Hey. We're gonna get our chance.
And when we do, I'm gonna park
you right on top of them.
[Amber]
Flight time is two and 20.
- Please eat something.
- [grunts]
Get some rest if you can.
[pills rattling]
What you got?
Provigil.
You got two to spare?
Appreciate it, brother.
Anyone else want to stay awake
- for the next three days?
- [Bobby] Yeah.
- Give me some of that shit.
- Yeah, I need one.
Oh, me, too.
- Hell yes.
- [Josie] Bet your ass
I want one of those.
Or take amphetamines.
[exhales]
That could also do the job.
♪ percussive music ♪
♪ tense music ♪
You want to drive,
or you want to shoot people?
- Shoot people.
- [chuckles]
How far is command?
Justice Center, 15 minutes.
Get us there in ten.
[engine starts]
♪
[clacking]
We thinking music,
or we rawdogging this drive?
Rawdog.
No music.
[exhales]
All right.
Strong and silent types.
I like it.
Look at the size
of that fucking thing.
[page turns]
When was this filed?
Fifteen minutes ago.
Uh, they filed it
when they landed.
Okay. I don't see
a departure time.
Didn't give us one.
They said owners are flakes.
Yeah, well, it's not valid
without a departure time.
[Grady]
Kyle.
I'm no aviation expert...
but I'll bet
that fucking thing can go
right across the Atlantic.
♪ uneasy music ♪
♪
How can I help you gentlemen?
No need to come up.
I'll come down to you.
No, we'll come up.
Yeah, I need to see
your flight manifest.
[captain] They can show you
in the office, sir.
It's been filed,
all the necessary documents,
they have it.
[door opens]
St. Martin
your final destination?
Yes, that is correct, sir.
St. Martin.
[Kyle]
"Karen Gold,
Michael Gold, Matthew Gold,
John Gold."
Fucking kidding me?
That's the best
you can come up with?
Sir, I can't have you in there,
I'm afraid.
- Hey, what are you doing?!
- I didn't ask
- your fucking permission!
- What is this, huh?!
- [Cody J] Hey, stay down.
- Stay down.
[captain]
Hey! Okay, okay, okay!
We good?
Oh, you're loaded full.
[chuckles] You don't need
44,000 pounds of fuel
to get to St. Martin. That's a
four-hour flight, 20,000 pounds.
Why are you trucking
the extra fuel?
[Cody J] There's food service
for five meals times three.
One passenger don't get a meal?
Where are you really going?
You can see the manifest
and flight plan.
- You can read, can't you?
- This isn't a charter
who owns this fucking plane, huh?
Oh.
Oh, you don't have
the answer for that?
Well, watch how fast I get
that fucking answer.
♪ low, tense music ♪
[Kyle breathing heavily]
Ah.
[chuckles]
Indonesian-based plane.
- Oh.
- Yeah, 'cause people
are flying from the South
Pacific to the fucking Caribbean
- all the time.
- Hey, hey, hands
- where I can see 'em.
- Hey, hey, okay!
Where I can fucking see 'em!
Okay, you got it! Okay!
[Kyle]
Aldhemi Aviation Corporation
in fucking Estonia.
An Estonian jet hangared
in Indonesia.
Goddamn it, I'm getting curious.
Are you getting curious?
Oh, I stay curious.
[quietly]
Brother,
I am getting fucking flanked
out here.
- [groans]
- You're on captain.
Hands
where I can fucking see 'em!
Right fucking now!
Go left. Hands up, motherfucker!
[sighing]
Send FBI my way.
I'm jackpot on the plane.
We got four bandits down.
[panting]
[sighs]
Okay, there's another one
up here on the right: 1117.
All these houses
look the fucking same.
They are all the same.
Yeah, this is it.
Don't look like anyone's home.
Don't look like anyone lives in
this whole fucking neighborhood.
We're at 1117 Hudson.
No vics in the driveway.
No evidence
this house is in use.
I can check the garage
- and around back.
- Can you bring Bravo up
on satellite?
Okay, proceed to 2210 Preston.
Check 'em all
and then work backwards.
Hunt the low-hanging fruit
first.
Roger that.
Want drive-bys on all of 'em
- before we start looking deeper.
- No, no, no.
It's better we sweep 'em first,
check 'em off the list.
Agreed.
Command, we'd rather work 'em
over one by one,
know they're clean
before we move on.
No, we do not live in that world
and we don't have the time.
You put eyes on
all your locations in your pod
and then you work backwards
through them.
[chuckles]
Right, because a chick in a suit
staring at a fucking computer
knows best.
I hear you, brother.
All right.
♪ low, tense music ♪
Renat.
A second.
You need a new out.
They're circling.
[man speaks foreign language
on phone]
That's not our problem.
That's your problem.
Now come get your problem
before we throw her
in the fucking street.
♪ somber music ♪
Just give me a chance.
Just give me a fucking chance.
[indistinct radio transmission]
Hey!
We up?
Not yet. We found the plane.
We found it and we shut it down.
- Was she on it?
- No.
But their out is fucked.
Got to make a new one
on the move.
They want us ready. Stand by.
I'm ready.
[sighs]
All we need is a chance.
No, I know.
We'll get it, we'll get it.
But, hey, listen to me.
Cool heads
when the chance comes, right?
Slow is smooth
and smooth is fast.
Not as fast as me.
[chuckles]
You know, I've been with her
for 15 years.
Ain't nobody wants her back
more than me.
I want her back more.
Thought you hated her.
How can I hate her?
She made me.
♪ low, tense music ♪
Your problem now.
[panting]
- Hey, hey.
- Okay, okay.
Don't fucking touch me.
[groaning]
[grunts]
[muffled grunt]
[gasps, groans]
[grunts, coughs]
[spits]
[panting]
My name is Babat.
I am here to take you
to your death.
But before your death...
...I want you to know...
...whole villages of men...
will crawl over you.
Rape will become so familiar,
you could just sleep through it.
And then we will bury you
to your neck...
...and little children
will stone you
to the edge of death.
But I will not let them
kill you.
You will beg me for death
before it comes.
But when I give it,
your death will be fire.
You see,
when the body is on fire,
it does not go into shock.
You will feel it all.
You will feel it
burn the flesh from your bones.
Your eyes will explode
from the heat.
You will feel it.
You will feel every bit of it.
"Bah-but."
Hmm?
"Baw-bat."
Sounds like the word...
...my daughter made up
when she took her first shit
in the toilet.
[chuckles]
They make warriors
of their women.
[Babat]
Oh.
Maybe so.
Watch me make a woman
of this warrior.
[breathing heavily]
[shuddering]
[breathing quickens]
[screaming]
[Babat]
That's not a warrior scream.
That's a woman scream.
That the whole neighborhood
can hear.
[screaming continues]
You motherfucker!
[muffled screaming]
You take her
and you take her now.
We're working on a new way out.
I don't care about your way.
My job was to get her here.
She's here.
The rest is your job.
[speaking Farsi]
[Joe groaning]
[speaks Farsi]
[groaning continues]
[muffled screaming]
♪ tense music ♪
♪
[starts engine]
♪ somber music ♪
♪ tense music ♪